

+38 099 300 56 05 kuchin.ihor@gmail.com

Telegram: Ihor\_ik Linkedin: Ihor Kuchin github.com/ik-web

Vyshneve, Kyiv Ready to work remotely

# **SUMMARY:**

I'm a frontend developer with a huge desire to learn new and improve. Currently, I'm looking for a new challenging project to develop myself even more. I have profound knowledge of HTML5/CSS3 including preprocessors (Sass/Less), a good understanding of responsive web design, and proficiency in working with native JavaScript (Typescript) & Frameworks (React, Redux). Also, I'm ready to learn new technologies. Currently interested in NextJS, Vue, MobX. I have experience in website layout and developing interfaces for web applications. More than 10 years of experience in sports formed in me a good understanding that persistence and stable work lead to good results.

# **SKILLS:**

- ✓ Typescript, JavaScript (ES2015 2019)
- React, Redux
- Fetch, REST API, SQL
- ✓ Algorithms: Solved 29 katas on CodeWars
- **⊘** Basic OOP understanding
- ✓ VS Code, WebStorm, Photoshop, Figma, Avocode
- Chrome Developer Tools (incl. React), Trello, Jira

# **EXPERIENCE:**

# **Frontend Developer**

Self employed, Apr 2021 - Present

Responsibilities: Development of interfaces for web applications.

Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, React, Redux, Next.js, WebSocket

## HTML / CSS developer

Freelance, Sep 2021 - present

Responsibilities: Layout of websites, landing pages etc.
Technologies: Git, HTML, CSS, JS, JQuery, Bootstrap, Bulma

## Capoeira teacher

Grupo Senzala de Capoeira, Sep 2018 - present

## Responsibilities:

- Group training of children and adults in the martial art of capoeira
- Individual training of adults in the martial art of capoeira

## Key accomplishments:

- Participation in competitions
- Certificates

#### Owner of an online store

IK-Shop, Sep 2018 - Mar 2020

## Responsibilities:

- User interface development
- Administration
- Promotion
- Work with clients

Technologies or Tools: HTML, CSS, JS, Facebook Ads, Google Ads

# **ADDITIONAL EDUCATION:**

- Frontend course at Mate academy (Git, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, React, Web)

- Learn.javascript.ru (JavaScript)
- Reactjs.org

# **PORTFOLIO:**

See some of my projects at:

[Link to portfolio page]

# **EDUCATION:**

### **Kyiv Trade and Economic College**

Merchandising and commercial activity

# **ACHIEVEMENTS:**

- **⊘** Capoeira fighter (12 years experience, level reached: instructor)
- ✓ Capoeira teacher (4 years experience, achievement: have certified students)